Student Affairs, Division for; Records ua730
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Division of Student Affairs Records
1926-2005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua730
18.33 cubic ft.
Contains the records of the Division of Student Affairs, its subordinate offices, and its predecessor bodies, including the Office of the Dean of Students. Materials include: planning and policy documentation, admissions and financial aid statistics, correspondence, and meeting minutes.
Administrative History
The Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs was created in 1965 to oversee a variety of aspects of student life at the University, including: residental life, counseling, athletics, financial aid, student activities, and health services. Most of these duties had previously been overseen by the Deans of Men and Women. The position of Vice President for Student Affairs was replaced by the Dean of Student Affairs (also referred to as Dean of Students) in 1972; the position reverted to a Vice Presidency in 1983. The Office was later renamed the Division of Student Success, but as of 2017 it is once again referred to as the Division of Student Affairs.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the work of the Division of Student Affairs Records and its predecessor offices. At different times the Division has overseen student counseling and student recreation, meaning these areas are documented as well. Recreation and athletics, particularly the University's move to Division I in the 1990s, is documented. A significant amount of this collection, focused in the mid-1980s and 1990s, documents the correspondence of the Division's Vice President. This collection also contains records on a number of Task Forces and Committees that representatives from Student Affairs sat on, including, the SIRS Design Team, the Task Force on EOP and MRP Admissions, and the Committee to Evaluate University Alcohol Policies as well as others. There is also admissions information, including population-level information on accepted students and proposed enrollment growth rates for the University. The collection also contains event notices; five-year planning records; files from the Five-Quad Ambulance Service and other student groups; and various other records pertaining to the administration of student affairs and activities at the University. Finally, the collection contains of files of correspondence and planning documents and pfrom the offices of the Deans of Men and Women, who oversaw many of the Division's responsibilities before the 1960s.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection has been arranged based upon labels on the original boxes when collection was transferred to the archives. Files in this collection were maintained in this original order and as such are not arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Student affairs services; Student affairs administrators; Education, Higher--Administration; College discipline; Administrative records; Correspondence; UAlbany Student Affairs; State University of New York at Albany
- Guide to Living Off Campus, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- University Senate Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Judicial Policies, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Student Affairs, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Student Association Budget, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Committee to Evaluate Alcohol Policy, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- FSA Financial Statements and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Faculty Handbook, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Student-Faculty Grievance Procedures, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Judicial WorkShop, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Student Judiciary Proposal, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Administrative Committee, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Administrative Communications Group, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Affirmative Action, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Campus Safety, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fire Safety Clippings, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fire Safety Consulting Team, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- DayCare Center Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alumni Office Placement, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Policies on Student Records, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Student Demonstrations, 1969-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Potter Club Newsletter, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Buckley Amendment, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- EOP/MRP Task Force, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- SIRS Summary Report, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- SIRS Design Team Diagrams [1 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- SIRS Design Team Diagrams [2 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- SIRS Design Team Diagrams [3 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- SIRS Design Team Binder#1 [1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- SIRS Design Team Binder#1 [2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- SIRS Implementation Binder, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Five Quad Ambulance Administration [1 of ], 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Five Quad Ambulance Administration [2 of ], 1984-1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Five Quad Ambulance Administration [3 of 4], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Five Quad Ambulance Administration [4 of 4], 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Squad Alumni, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Five Quad Ambulance Correspondence, 1975-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Five Quad Chief's Reports, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Five Quad Vehicle Purchases, 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Five Quad Board Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Five Quad Board Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Five Quad Memoranda, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Five Quad Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 5 Quad, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Dining Services Master Plan Report, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Five Quad By laws and Meeting Minutes, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Admissions/Fin. Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- PEAR, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Counseling Annual Reports, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- PEAR Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Data Summaries, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Affirmative Action Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Student Services, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Residential Life/Housing, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- O.V.P.S.A, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Admissions and Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Administrative Services Annual Report, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Campus Life, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Health and Counseling, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Programs, Priorities and Assessing a Decade, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Five-Year Plan, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Admissions, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Department of Academic Support Services Resource Materials, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Academic Support Services Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Academic Support Services Resource Document, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Division of Physical Education Five Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Five Year Plan Update, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 5-Year Plan Progress Reports, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Campus Life, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Residential Life/Housing, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Health and Counseling, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Student Services, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Vice President's Office, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- PEAR, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Undergraduate Admissions Annual Report, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Five Year Plan Update, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Five-Year Plan, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Student Life Committee, 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- President's Management Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Committee on Racial Concerns Across the Campus (Nepaulsingh Chair), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Advisory Committee on Racial Concerns, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chief Student Affairs Administrators February 13-14, 1986 - Albany, 1986 February 13-14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chief Student Affairs Administrators Fredonia, NY June 6-7, 1989, 1989 June 6-7 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Women's Safety Awareness, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- World Week, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Yearbook (Torch), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Volunteers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- VANDALISM, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Vacancy Reports, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- UAS, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- University Senate, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- University Council, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Undergraduate Studies, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Drug-Free Schools Brochure, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Academic Support Programs and Services Brochure (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Bills/Checks World Week II, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- World Week Registration & Program, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- World Week IV Recepits, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- General Info for World Week, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- World Week Recommendations, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- World Week, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- World Week 86 Budget, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Program + Publicity, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Block Party, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Committee Info., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- "Process" Memos, Forms, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Keynote Address + Reception, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- $$$$, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Room Reservations + Changes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Carmel's Notes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Extra Copies WW Letter to Dean's Directors & Chairs, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Equipment Request Originals, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Block Party, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Reimbursement Requests, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- WWIX Block Party, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Block Party, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Meeting Schedule Forms, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- World Week Program, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- World Week VIII Planning Minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- World Week X Extra RFPs, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- WWX, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- WWX Events/Prgm Forms, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- WWXI, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Program Registration Forms, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- WWIX Program Registration Forms, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Reimbursements, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- World Week VIII, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- WWIX Budget Correspondence, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Budget Memorandum, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- World Week IX, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- WWIX Advertisement Information, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- WWIX Copies, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- WWIX Pamphlets/Eval Info, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Publications, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Program and Publicity, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Room Reservations + Changes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Mariah's Notes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Keynote Address + Reception, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Committee Info., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Block Party, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Program Registration, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Budget, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Division of Student Affairs Progress Report, 1989-1993; 1990 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Establishment of the Just Community, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Just Community: Documents and Policies, Programming and Student Letters, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Just Community: Printing of Brochures, Pins, Posters, and Decals, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Just Community Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Research & Development Student Affairs, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Task Force for Women's Safety, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Basic Guide to Living off Campus, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Seminar on Racism, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Discretionary Budget Allocations, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Classrooms-Space, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Beloved Project, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Bus Service Task Force, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Budget (DOB) Hearing, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Educom, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Educational Development Task Force, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Hudson-Mohawk Association, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Brochure--Cultural Diversity, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Orientation Planning and Development Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Accreditation- U-Mass, Amherst, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Parents Weekend, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Parents Weekend, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Parents Weekend, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Parents Forum, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Safety, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- ACPA Convention, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Career Development Center, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Suny Advisory Coum. For Women Students, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- University Council, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Recruitment/ Retention, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- University Affairs, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- SUNYA Students Profile: Perscriptions, Altitudes,etc, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Academic Freedom Conference, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Ada Account, 1963-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Aida Craig Walker Award, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Aida Craig Walker, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Aida Craig, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Ada Craig Walker Nominations, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Ada, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Ada, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Ada Craig Walker, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Who's Who, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- M-Z Who's Who, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Who's Who, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Who's Who, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Who's Who, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Who's Who, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Who's Who, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Who's Who, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Who's Who, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Who's Who, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Who's Who, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Who's Who Application Materials and Evaluation Sheet, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Who's Who, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Who's Who, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Who's Who in American Colleges, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- St. Patrick Swygert Correspondence [1 of 3], 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- St. Patrick Swygert Correspondence [2 of 3], 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- St. Patrick Swygert Correspondence [3 of 3], 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- President Swygert, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [1 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [2 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [3 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [1 of 3], 1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [2 of 3], 1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Memoranda to Patrick Swygert [3 of 3], 1993 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Vice President Doellefeld's Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Day File Correspondence, 1996 January-1997 June (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Day File Correspondence, 1996 January-1996 August (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Day File Correspondence, 1995 May-1995 December (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- President Hitchcock's Correspondence, 1996 August-1997 June (Box 8, Folder 6)
- President Hitchcock's Correspondence, 1996 January-1996 August (Box 8, Folder 7)
- President Hitchcock's Correspondence, 1995 August-1995 December (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Publication Review and Approvals (Speaker Approvals), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Vietman Memorial Moving Wall, 1998 March (Box 8, Folder 10)
- President Clinton's Initiative on Race Campus Week of Dialogue, 1998 April (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Synergy, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 25th Annual Conference: The New SUNY: A University for Tomorrow, 1995 November (Box 8, Folder 13)
- SUNY Senior Student Affairs Administrators Meeting, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Chief Student Affairs Officers Association, 1996 March (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Transformational Leadership Conference College Student Personnel Association of New York State Inc. (CSPA), 1995 December (Box 8, Folder 16)
- ACT Annual Conference, 1996 November (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Seymour, Stephen, 1997 March (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Healthy Campuses: Celebrating Teamwork! A Statewide Conference, 1995 November (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Autumn Barbecue, 1996 October (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Project Renaissance, 1996 October (Box 8, Folder 21)
- LGBT Conference, 1996 April (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Diversity Week Program, 1996 March (Box 8, Folder 23)
- MSAC Meeting AD 253, 1995 November (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Class Officers Luncheon w/ President Hitchcock, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Barbecue At President's Home, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Media Tip-Off Luncheon, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Meeting With G.S.O & President, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Meeting With S.A. President, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Reception for University Student Leaders, 1996 September (Box 8, Folder 30)
- President's Reception for Student Leaders, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Central Council Meeting, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Student Association Officers, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Homecoming/Family Weekend Unity Dinner Sponsored by Student, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Graduate Student Organization, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Holloween Barbecue, 1997 October (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Student Association Officers, 1997 November (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Graduate Student Organization, 1997 November (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Student Association Officers, 1997 December (Box 8, Folder 39)
- President's Planned Times With Students, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- University Life Council, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- University Council, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Cabinet Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Cabinet Meetings, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cabinet Mailings, Fall 1996-Spring 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Cabinet Mailings, 1995 May-1995 December (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Directors/ Cabinet Correspondence, 1995 May-1995 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
- SUNY-A Study of Student Health Services, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Articles, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Public Safety, 1991-1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Public Safety UPD, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Administration Services Status Report, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- UPD Chief Search, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Student Death Responses, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Student Death Memoranda, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Residential Life, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Press Releases and Statistical Releases, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Admissions- Statistical Releases, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Admissions, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Admissions, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Admissions, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Admissions Numbers, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Admissions Statistics, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Institutional Research Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Institutional Research Reports, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Admissions Report, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Cabinet (Executive), 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Cabinet Meeting Minutes, 1984-1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Disabled Student Services, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Budget Report, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- ADA Craig Walker Award, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- ADA Craig Walker Award, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Budget, Fall, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Student Affairs Budget, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- English Class, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Student Affairs Cabinet, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Empire State Games, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Empire State Games Olympic Village, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Empire State Games, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Empire State Games, 1991 July (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Empire State Games, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Empire State Games, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Empire State Games, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Financial Aid and Scholarship, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Financial Aid, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- GSO, 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Graduate Assistants, 1989-1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Health Center, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Health and Counseling Services, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Personal Safety and Off Campus Affairs, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Safety Security Initiatives, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Safety-Security, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Personal Safety and Off Campus Affairs [1 of 3], 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Personal Safety and Off Campus Affairs [2 of 3], 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Personal Safety and Off Campus Affairs [3 of 3], 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- System Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- System Administration, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- SUNY Central Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- UPD to Police Stations, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Planning Themes, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Five-Year Plan Progress Reports, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Five-Year Plan Progress Updates, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Five-Year Plan, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Planning Themes, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Student Activities, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Student Affairs- 5yr Plan Update, 1984 January (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Office of Student Affairs, 1965-1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Student Affairs, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Student Affairs, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Student Activities, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Student Affairs, Dean, 1966-1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Student Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Athletics Files, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Lighten vs. SUNYA, 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lighten vs. SUNYA, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Lighten vs. SUNYA, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lighten vs. SUNYA, Undated; 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Inaugural Committee, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- DIFR, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- DIFFR Zero Base Budget Initial Report, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Kane V. SUNY, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Students vs. Athletics Case, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- 1993- Just Community Brochure- Original Photos, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Presidential Search, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- System Administration, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Just Community Approach Presentation, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Public Safety, 1982-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- President's Cabinet, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Task Force: Parties, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Retreat (Cabinet), 1993 June (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Retreat (Cabinet), 1993 August (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Retreat (Cabinet), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) On-Campus Recruiting File, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Athletics Facilities, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Drug and Alcohol Use on Campus [1 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Drug and Alcohol Use on Campus [2 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Alcohol Policy, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Alcohol Policy and Development, 1983-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Athletics General, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Athletics Files [1 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Athletics Files [2 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Athletics Salary Adjustments, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Athletics Department Materials [1 of 3], 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Athletics Department Materials [2 of 3], 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Athletics Department Materials [3 of 3], 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- SIRS Procedure Manual [1 of 4], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- SIRS Procedure Manual [2 of 4], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- SIRS Procedure Manual [3 of 4], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- SIRS Procedure Manual [4 of 4], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Athletics, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Athletics, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Athletics, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Athletics, 1984-1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Athletics, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Knicks, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Athletics Department Policies and Procedures Manual, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Division II Athletics Proposal, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Athletics Memoranda [1 of 2], 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 13)